the health bar
yeah we're live and we have one viewer
it's giving them all a minute to show up
is there a word for like periscope ease
Scopus we gotta we gotta wait for the
skull piece to come off
Oh George you know what I wanted the
team to get you for Christmas
what a like a handheld selfie stick that
you can like film around with oh yeah
this is the I'm happy to control
so little not calibrated it looks great
yeah what about to be a tool here we
have a tool thing though we have a thing
yeah
oh we do can you get open polar drivers
right to the fast-track plane oh we have
to get it out by the way people are
asking what's different with zero point
just look at it Bros Bros that whose
money is this mine did I not say it's
mine right yeah we have a fast track oh
nice love it love it
prepared um so yeah I know what's Devon
with 0.4 just and what got it right
landscape cycles all right yeah Thibault
don't switch him along the scope he's
don't like that okay take a look
right
so see 0.4 is not out yet we are going
to be driving with it and finding bugs
during the whole trip and then we will
release it so I'm gonna disengage here
at a faster
listen to next of the warm
oh no the other one also that disengages
pretty nice disengaged yeah
I just get back up to speed oh no it's
just traffic okay
so unfortunately guys you know how I
have to move you know how I have cool
firmware flashes Pacific won't happen
you for the Raval are so yeah the rav4
doesn't work at speeds below 20 miles an
hour right now
um this is also true and release open
pilot too but you know we're not gonna
release EPS flashes but PCM flashes were
a lot more violent so yeah we got about
a five minute traffic already can join
us for the traffic no this looks good
we're chillin with our scope he's the
hallway um yes and welcome to the common
self driving awareness tour we're
getting a much later start than we
thought yeah um because oh man we
would've left two hours earlier if we
didn't talk about physics for two hours
I lost I lost $100 if you throw a ball
off of the ISS it will not go back to
earth yes it takes a lot of Delta VD to
return to Earth okay we're back engaged
here
for over 20 years over the remain in
orbit that's what hairless
like The Herald was right that's why you
wanted we have smart people are coming
[Music]
today
he did he did he I think that Cory Cory
as Cory's come a personal chef so what
do you guys do what do you think of the
new UI we're the hearts come from I
don't know I think that you can tap that
you love it oh you tap can you turn off
the video playing and sugar plus it's
illegal in my state to have video
playing up front yeah what do you want
instead you want ways you can dress you
can go two ways you can go to Spotify
we haven't even linked up the Bluetooth
right and what Catholic ology running
back down to I mean oh it's just whether
it's engaged or not right
so thanks ways that's right there on
your yawns oh we're back engaged here
well this great new UI come to me or is
it just shiver oh well we'll say I'm so
it is coming out with with open pile 0.4
yeah yawns yawns we'll get some of it
I'm just some event goods
I need us look at some of it
unfortunately you know Neos aren't that
great with the thermal and the new
version of Neos is not released yet
which kind of some of those defenses but
this is so this is the same as ship
applause the only difference the
chifforobe losses it doesn't actually
drive your car it's the dashcam the way
Spotify pretty much the same interface
down
come on available but I don't really
know them oh it's that comma unavailable
speech you love that's the that's the
warning we get in question about the
pigeon no no we don't have any pigeons
are delayed yeah production was young
productions alongside we yeah solid we
shimmy out we shipped out all the eons
today we don't talk about the number
it's huge I don't really don't know if
people think it's a lot who drives
George well technically you oh yeah I'm
Tom Drive so we just drive it you get a
control of this view at all times
completely this is not an autonomous
vehicle upcoming it oh my god it has two
L's wait really
I didn't even see that doesn't kids love
to else no no no your open windows at
your office that a growth could see your
whiteboard trump could see my white
throne a draw
well I think I wrote it before with
multiple else it has to elves I'm sure
do you look up it sounds like a British
spelling or something we're driving on
an eon for the person asking with all
Kamala
if you botany on it doesn't come with
bulk and pilot becomes + shift+ ways we
love to always experience the ways
experience has a few bugs honestly by
the time it gets to Google probably
defects cracked Americans prefer one and
Brits like to else what is the
difference between supercopa pilot great
question great question
open pilot actually controls your car
shiver Plus does not
this car needs to do needs to do stop
and go yeah
is that possible for it
is it possible we have to reflash the PC
so I need to install open pylon you can
if you want
you are completely on your own if you
make modifications we're not gonna stop
you can make modifications like kind of
what sort of a hypocrite would I be if I
tried to stop you from making
modifications to the products that you
paid for so the rap floor will come to a
full stop but which is a bit different
from the stock system well use a mutex
how's the priests coming if they crash
into each other I feel like a nice like
video Prince has launched zero 43.0 it
works it freezes when it says cancelled
yes you have to drive
yeah the stock system beeps once and
then you're just rolling on it'll
actually only cancel if it you want to
accelerate because it can break all the
way down to zero just can't accelerate
once you fall below 20 so this is why
it's only a PCM reflash PCM is the
powertrain control module they used to
use the word ECU engine control unit but
now everything is just the ECU it got
kind of genericized
watch out vehicles stopped on shoulder
ahead this ways tells me this one I wish
I could disable that alert because I've
never cared that there was a vehicle
stop on shoulder is the piece just as
good as the rav4 when she looking dirty
could put the clean is similar well
Windex will wear the shouting out bro
this one you have pull it towards you
again notice how it's filtering about
the exclusive t-shirts available for
sale in person on this tour let me tell
you something if kama succeeds that
t-shirts gonna be worth like 80 bucks on
ebay we're selling it for way less than
80 is 20 points are the border states we
like the border
got a good eye it like removes maybe
that was more party yeah
we gotta we gotta put place in Spotify
box
to your investors Confucian has improved
right lane these dots dots are hard
we're just as good as the have four
people keep asking similar sibling does
not do it does stop and go
the priestess I've got a box yeah you
actually stopped to press the button to
resume where's the little insects bees
for Nick beetles
I have some hearts like where's the
dislike yeah no dislike I'm yeah from
our perspective only love that's great
the connection drop does the device that
you shouldn't open presents dollop yep
yes the connection dropped Oh on on yeah
well I've iPhone accent o'clock club
chips unsecured chips now
our next trip will have Alex Roy right
Alex Alex Roy is a partner he is a
partner yes we could be a partner he's a
part what he'd be doing for you since
zero but that's the kind of partnership
some be like that's all I understand if
anybody out there wants to say that
they're a partner with comma AI you're
welcome to if your name is Alex Roy soon
better always dance man let's learn it
it's a little still not quite
calibrating we get more calibrated after
acknowledges yeah you get more caliber
therefore now basically Cowboys always
running
are you Chris packing a caffeine
we pack shipments in order you know what
attacked I packed my wallet my laptop
and my passport yeah it's all you need
mine
I know you know they check all your
passports those you won passport for
more than one task per person it's
sketchy I thought you couldn't do it
okay like a mini passport here to you
there's actually our state license which
will let you go to complain three one
mature states
what's point three one five two point
through it
a Michigan enhanced license that's a
thing
4:31 it's the legal ownership you guys
have for collision winning yes
oh but only if you're in a car where you
can connect to France so you need a
giraffe as well but chipper Blas
absolutely
a Washington also has in his hands to
license that works for Hannah thinks we
learned this is fascinating
so there must be a deal
federal government Michigan there's the
fridge from Detroit to Canada
yeah unconscious time
Detroit's a Cadillac crossed that bridge
from Canada to true and then I saw my
first house on fire my second house on
fire in a bring span of an hour I don't
know Detroit making a comeback yet yes
actually
actually yeah but it definitely is
beginning to come back there is always
rock-bottom a song called oh yeah you
know what happened to that house that
was on the front of the Marshall Mathers
LP like this old house they burned out
of course interesting so the bar isn't
getting reset when I up the sets eat on
the Toyota signs and kilometers for
Canadians that is kind all right we got
I always hit politically correct thing
so it's gonna stay with me yes
I don't think we should make such
accommodations to Canadians I think here
we have miles and there they have
kilometers and we should celebrate our
diversity yeah decent diversity what are
we gonna start working with multiple
cameras
what multiple cameras throw you got to
George should like Detroit because of
all the good rap I'd like to try I'm not
saying I don't like to try to just say
it I've seen two houses on fire in my
life one in Detroit and the next one in
Detroit 20 minutes later I almost would
do I almost want to a hip-hop Club in
Detroit that's what I was gonna do but I
was late for Chicago Wow
I was in Buffalo and I'm like oh man I
look up through Canada to get to Chicago
bad choice man Canada speed limits oh
god please
as they coming back across the border
they grilled me because I was like six
no no it was rude that was okay they
brought me into the room and stuff oh
wow because I was only in Canada for six
hours and they like what what to pick up
I'm driving to Chicago from Buffalo and
yeah and they're like your dumbest you
know it's like that takes two hours more
I'm like yeah I'm Canada and see the
nice Canadian sights
wait I've never I've never heard about
our free HD maps are absolutely free HD
maps existing to troll
deep map now honestly like TomTom deep
map here maps I want to see all these
companies go out of business because we
open-source something that is better
than what they have and like I don't
mean open trust like OpenStreetMap I
mean like just bsd-like do whatever you
want
when will we release them
thank you what do you think of Tessa
moving out of mobile I'd given that they
have good tap
um Tesla didn't move out of mobile I
mobile I terminated the relationship
with Tesla so it's not like Tesla had a
choice what do I think of mobile i
severing ties with Tesla that all
depends how mobile I thinks of
themselves that's one way to think about
it is yeah you're gonna sell another
300,000 chips you know making 50 bucks a
chip you're looking at you're looking at
revenue you look at a profit there's
another way of saying those chips are
gonna help them more transition to be
one of our competitors so I mean I think
mobilize boomers are insecure I didn't
so it wasn't a stress
I'm a competitor in the sense they're
gonna take some well they're taking a
chunk of it
like they're not gonna start test if I
gotta sell the other
what's nice exciting thing we can avail
on this would you actually what which is
actually why mobile I should have showed
us ultimate yeah maybe they'll get
hooked they might continue to ship the
chip forever yeah no I mean there's
actually the key distinction if you
believe that Tesla wasn't gonna ship a
competing from any future cars coming
for 2018 any what feature cars I'm
assuming it's up to more cars I don't
know is true as an honest man oh yeah
we'll be doing will be doing all the
Toyotas we're gonna like rent a camera
to crawl and make that work though
as long as you see this bar keep going
down I'm not touching the wheel the gas
or the brakes we test something
the microphone works on it yawns yeah
it's a great thing on software updates
man okay
George how hard do you think would be to
get a car without Lane keep assist to
work with open pilot depress the car I
think that GM is you can kind of do it
because they seem to have shift the
steering command even on cars without
outcasts on the Honda's it's disabled in
the steering firmware so you'd have to
do a reflash in the Toyota's I don't
know but almost all of them Chevrolet
keep so security updates 40.4 security
we had a security
kind of security and then top five
bathrooms Oh your top five rappers man
yo Drake drinks the best rapper alive
not little peep go index the way Eminem
has fallen I do and that I do I do
LP to was just like what forgiving your
mom Oh
security is like people stealing your
car like oh I'm a security no we'll get
to that next year yeah I'm sensing a
little bias here I like that good vibes
yes a little
all the best rappers used to be big in
the world it's just like that's a new
thing man you don't want to be an
oppressor you want to be a little biased
is that is that a real thing no no that
is a bad thing
why who will buy if I get it no we are
friends with all of the regulators you
like regulate when you like regulators
we don't like formed when to expect to
reflash for Toyota so we had to
disengage I mean before it used to be
because you know this is actually faster
than your go ankle stop unless we tell
you the actual speed Oh these match no
this doesn't match this this this tells
you the actual see unlike your carbon
it's so stupid that they don't tell you
the actual your car is your trip
you yeah most most speedometers
and cars read 2% faster than you're
actually yelling they do this so
basically you can't try to get Toyota to
pay your ticket for you oh it doesn't
actually work it's not like you can even
say yeah why would you ever raise money
um so we don't have a fudge factor on
the speed you know come on we're
engineers right we're putting the real
speed that's how fast your cars going
okay
and the distance the distance to your
lead car will always be in meters this
was briefly changed to feet you might
even see the comment and you I if you
really want feet you can open source it
but I said meters for forever even when
you change but there's still a metric
slides
where did the name come from there is a
metrics or the name of a comma come from
uh you know if you don't have a
successful company it's got to be like
between like four nine letters and two
syllables mom go
Facebook fan control seems on and off
yeah the fan is a little policy we
couldn't probably rewrite the policy to
do better it's open source check out the
code and manager you can check out
shipper plus is already released the new
chef for plus so you can go to a github
comedy applause before chef replaces
already released Oh like I said the end
of the trip on the end of the trip after
we you know track it make sure there's
no above like yeah do test on all cop
cars yes we tested on all comic cards
though I think 0.4 you're gonna have to
manually update to because we are no
longer testing Neo compatibility we're
only going to test Aeon compatibility it
should still work on the O's but we'll
leave that up to the community
every dollar cars get daily used yeah
boys
I named this car autumn yeah look at the
seats it's very very fitting
[Music]
oh yeah hard that driver's seat is
pretty that's why we get the premium
package
[Laughter]
I really wish this thing work and stop
and go yeah but the good news is I don't
think there's gonna be much traffic
where we're going bro Nebraska doesn't
even know what that word means demos in
LA in LA I hear there's no more party
[Music]
video of that guy who was like talking
about house parties to some town hall
meeting and he was like they were
thinking about shutting down house
parties and he was like me and my Bros
really love house parties let me tell
you did you guys not see this video no
oh you would love it you would it's like
the funniest that yeah I will show it to
you once we're done periscoping it fruit
those periscope e's they should take a
look at a world war rush cookies to be
like you know how like cutie pie is like
cool guy to browse the internet with
yeah 140 most copies that's a big road
trip man we need a bus to fit all
at 40 mine I don't know hearty books you
guys can play the license-plate game
with us though I've ever been on a party
bus yeah the 1i Manhattan once I get
ahead like buses get around the no
seatbelt
they're like part of the government some
some actually do seatbelts okay Lane no
yes school buses have seatbelts that
like law changed some coach just
seatbelt helps you wanna bus if it flips
what it's gonna hold you in your seat by
your seatbelt I don't think that's how
seat belts work man their construction
is actually saver so they don't require
a seat belt you continue at that train
of thought we're a little confused with
the construction part yeah like their
frames probably
flying through the air like through the
front windshield well you'll kind of hit
the seat in front of you right they're
supposed to plate could lake lake lake
mostly well it depends what kind of
collision you're really talking about
right you let's the other thing too like
if you're talking about like a multi
vehicle collision the bus doesn't move
that much never seen a car in a bus yeah
I don't like if a bus hits a tree well
no but again you're still like okay so
say you're in like the middle seat of
the bus right like momentum is all it's
just like you know your velocity right
so see even the whole front of the bus
crumples right this is why you sit on
the back of the bus kids always wondered
where is the safest place to sit in an
airplane but turns out there is no
safety spot so no I actually heard that
it's safer in the in the in the back
oh or maybe like by the wing it's
probably the safest the front not always
I think the front is substantially less
safe I think when you look at likes like
the the well yeah would you look at like
their plane crashes that people did
survive I think they were like balloons
are probably your best bet the backs
pretty good the Front's not good you
know but that's the thing man you got to
decide what you care about
[Music]
I like I like flying first class that's
all I'll say I have done it you know got
a free upgrade because I was hungry
there was a meal and she was like no and
I just had like the biggest look of like
oh my god what am I gonna do I'm late
for my flight it's just like click some
buttons and was just like okay your
upgrade to enjoy your flight that's like
that stuff like that happens it doesn't
happen to me sometimes Eddie yeah
do you wish we lived in a capitalist
society where we could just bid on that
seat I flip four times in a bus only out
of bloody lip Wow bro family car why are
we taking a bus here this feels like a
family car totally buses buses are
actually super safe yeah buses are
trains which is more safe a train I
think well they derail so that's we
don't I don't I know you don't I don't
know accidents versus deaths there's
different view horrifying training
ye truths could be so safe because
self-driving trains are so easy but
unions are literally killing people no
so I took the train home last year and I
took the tracks and like Chicago to DC
those dirty was fast enough and safe
enough so no like I should sue the train
company butt off serious bump oh I got
woken up out of my sleep and I landed
weirdly on my elbow man that's so freaky
honestly sometimes on Cal train I feel
like the conductor goes way too fast no
no this is way worse than like any train
I've ever been on the ride from
California to Chicago wasn't right but I
took the weird route so I didn't take
Chicago to New York I'm like well it's
less money or I get more time on the
train I have a really sweet sleeper
cabbagey time I went through like DC up
to New York I think the Cardinal if you
guys are Amtrak fans
damn tragedies no no no people on the
train or like Europeans who don't know
Americans don't take the train yeah yeah
drug smugglers and Tom oh we should have
had a GoPro camera attached separately
to create a time-lapse video of the
whole trip that sounds like a lot of
work and charging the battery and
keeping all that you know you know what
you know what we have a camera to create
a time-lapse video of the whole trip
it's built into the seal this is all
getting uploaded right now
why would I train also finds a terrible
experience no it wasn't about these fit
the train was literally something to do
the Train cost me more than flying and
took more time it's a journey it's not
about enjoy the journey shout out to
Kelly for that she doesn't watch these
unfortunate watch I skull piece I don't
thinks she's not one of our skull piece
Vanessa that she's on when I'm gonna
give her a holler and Tyler watch it
[Music]
yeah every week what's the most fun
[Laughter]
[Music]
buses no little bit how many others a
dumbass is being hit by trains you have
to separate you know no suicide by train
I don't know maybe I'm biased SEO
stories about Palo Alto the like there
how many people were killed on the tree
think that's what this numbers this is
do the trains no no what we're gonna
change the way we do the timer when we
switch model architectures
Tigers go fees grab 37 37
you know the pedestrian killed by a
train
this is open pilot it's not how over
here I'm not driving you guys yeah I
mean I'm driving over control of the
vehicle at all times I am monitoring the
system but the system is operating the
steering wheel brake and gas just like
an adaptive cruise control ranking
system but good no new time around 0.4
no zero before it's got the same timer
0.4 we changed some of them just the way
things are managed to grab CJ see you I
see that pink pink means the car is
doing it now if I take over colors man
our designer follow us on Twitter and
absolutely
how do i factory such heartbeats that
money on to install fresh shipper plus
again thrown in so fresh different plus
you can go to recovery mode by holding
power and volume down and then it's just
I am engine mod recovery you could just
say reset that wipes the data partition
you'll be reset with the US Senate
when your Eon arrived so it should be
shortly yeah there you know we should
ship the Bell
when do you think you'll add support for
flying cars Oh show us a fine car after
we built you oh you know what I did see
the life-size drone economy yeah
switches to work okay it's like it's
like can you unplug or plug in a hard
drive all the computers on it you can
the best idea baa
now if you want to if you want to switch
back to the stock system
there's time yes which is at the same
time
maybe if we run into one of you on the
tour we can try this almost Raven Falls
go
I'm gonna wake up tomorrow and I think
Skokie's is inspired and brilliant or
terrible yeah I've done it doesn't hurt
the car quotes which just stop now
won't push the stock okay it's not gonna
hurt they it's surprisingly hard to hurt
cars
like if we actually track the percent
that open pilot is driving although it's
gonna be driving for over 99% more
yeah 99 well I never said of the miles
Oh with the stop-and-go thing yeah this
topic I think it's actually probably a
bit less certainly like over 95 percent
and that's why guys you know you know of
all about fact-checking the media
whenever you see like Delfy claiming
that they did a ninety nine percent of
time of his trip across the country they
did on basically this is 99 percent
autonomous as well the last 1% with all
the hard stuff
[Music]
we should actually figure it out wait
yeah we can actually do it we can see
what percent the system was engaged for
me
maybe we'll do the impulsion some
statistics disengagement is what caused
disengagement stuff in it would be sweet
put Trump in charge of your stats it'll
be the best the best that's number one
stats has 100%
waynebow there they probably could they
probably could
when was the only company that can watch
Elon backed up a little bit on his claim
that he's going to do it I didn't we'll
see we'll see I'm rooting for him but if
I was a betting man
if auger had its prediction markets live
and one of them was is Tesla gonna make
it across the country and it was set at
50/50 either way we meet deadlines I
think pigeons are in the soon TM
oh really hi i'm leanna Jeff Bezos fan I
am I have like no Japanese ji electric
business
[Music]
uber talented I am a collective fan how
am i do I pronounce that I think it's so
let's let's let's see what happens when
we run out of health bar it's gonna go
our yeah we'll say
yeah I have a lot of options
use your face Oh
still there sorry you're so gross
though it's really appreciative it yeah
what did you do I didn't do anything
done anything oh there you go taken told
you look at that LD a steering wheel ok
so now let's let it run out what we do
it well and I won't slow down it'll stop
accelerating right so effectively we go
limp on the gas but for safety reasons
we continue to do the brake in the
steering wheel right like you know
[Music]
take control - against Peter I'm gonna
take control I'm gonna listen to it
yeah good so when we do that that was
good when we do replace the health bar
we are going to punish you for not
paying attention and now I'm taking
control by light log outs yeah it's
gonna be kind of like hey man take
control even when you don't need to this
is how we make sure that the user stays
though the system isn't good enough yet
for this to be a threat but all with our
new head of machine learning don't think
we'll announce who it is but we have a
new head of machine learning starting
next year right Tom used to it I don't
think we should if Tom blows his own
cover that's on top yeah
Oh
why is it always telling us you know
normally yeah that's useful I handed
about the car on the shoulder please
tell me about the police police up ahead
I thank you which I really like to know
that feel better I feel like I got one
step on the police please don't step on
me you know what we should give back to
waste that's a great way to give back to
ways what's what's your so that's Auto
reports please yeah it's like we could
have Auto reported that place let's put
that in let's put that in class let's
put that in driving ideas yeah no it's
good way to get back twice to estimated
date for Camry with gssb compatibility
soon TM to be honest you can I'm sure if
you rented a Camry and like know how to
code even a little bit you can make it
work I think it's really close to the
ground floor
cops apparently monitor ways to throw
like wow like for the cops on stuff
damn so we gotta have yeah we gotta have
at the new this is just an arms race man
now the truth isn't any arms raised
privacy news isn't openness wins the
location of the cops will eventually be
on one great moroder's man I solemnly
swear I am up to no good
right who gets my Harry Potter
Wow y'all seen Star Wars or I didn't
know honestly I shouldn't say this out
loud is Kobe's we're supposed to be cool
to hang out with man like Disney
to see like 1 2 3 but everybody
needs to see four or five and six and I
understand yeah I learned that there are
forty hours everyone we're in the middle
of nowhere wait
40 hours of footage uploaded to YouTube
every minute under every day
I have never watched is not illegal
really is not okay to be honored that's
right when I was 19 and I had it when I
was 18 and I had a van I drove across
all Nebraska watching Veronica Mars
to be I'm sure if that was illegal I'm
sure the statute of limitations has way
expired I have had upper drivers who are
watching something while drive okay
that's that's read stars man
three stars two stars no you either give
one serve five stars you can't be that
it no no no no I definitely give
in-between yeah all the time I've never
given a one star
I've given I think I've given one one
side where it's just like because the
thing is they match you if you give them
if you give them anything lower than two
you don't get matched with them again
and if I really didn't like something
someone did I don't want to be matched
well why did someone do to deserve a one
star rating oh he turned off the
navigation and you need to direct me
like I can direct you but and then you
like turn it on again and then drove if
that's a horrible reason to give someone
I gave a guy to star who literally
deliberately drove around the same block
twice to get a higher fare he didn't get
a higher fare to severe a day was not
back in the day he used to not be this
is back in Miami well okay I also feel
bad about giving lower stars because
their rating is really affected on
whether or not they can drive yep
don't feel the whole point of it is to
like avoid the kind of like someone who
drives like like not smoothly I get four
stars to like if that's my only someone
who someone who drives in a way I
consider not the safest I give three
stars to someone who deliberately
with me I give two stars too and some
other doesn't get me where I'm going or
like doesn't be so terrible that's what
I would do for one star but yeah I don't
think we've ever gotten there
one guy one quite drivers absolutely
asleep at a stop sign
yeah I would say this is this that's it
that's it oh you guys what's your rating
because it says a lot about you for a
second 804 savita's mojo chlorine mine
249 you guys just a broad category you
know why because I'm a very pleasant
person in cars no black mare yo I think
that's the Burger King that I stopped
that for a whopper
on the way to self-raising cars part 2
what happened there false positive
breaking events what do you guys feeling
Eddie should we sit down the Kali and
sit down family restaurant and eat some
pecans in the park or get some big
dollars in the park whoever remembers
that by the way yeah
we will notice what you have a new AI
model oh they do the hollows off the new
model is going to be unreal man you'll
notice that it drives completely without
lanes you'll be able to like it'll work
on like residential streets
that's what I was good
we don't and our new or new head of
machine learning is gonna make them
incredible yes I hope he watches I hope
you watches this and realizes how much
trust and faith yeah yeah that's gonna
make you an MLA dude well I do know
since we have prototypes we got to just
finish implementing it soon - yep Anna
pigeons will happen first
so consider the pigeon to be the canary
in the coalmine
no we're going to need to get some
pigeons out there in order to gather
some higher precision data that's why I
see Izzie oh yeah because o because it
says demo oh my god I forgot that we're
not Stella we got a drive really soon
you're gonna do that anyway
alright it we can't watch Star Wars
that's right try that will you keep your
eyes when you're driving
I've never been to a Cracker Barrel
Jackie and I looked at a Cracker Barrel
and we didn't think any of the food was
healthy of course not but you know kitty
pryde has a great line about a cracker
bow we ought to Christmas that's all
that's all that kitty pryde Dead Island
by Kitty Pryde should get herself into
Kitty Pryde changed name to kitty she
dropped her prize but you know why she
mustered a lover you know why though
maybe she's scared of being served by
Marvel it won't drive to the Kitty Pryde
character yeah see look it just have
like a greenish tint to everything now
or is that just like an optical because
if you just focus on the structure like
just put your that should go away right
away that's above can you add that drag
feedback oh it should juicer distracted
should go away literally as soon as I
correct
yeah George because if you look at it
without the green background assessment
I say
or Reno
in between Sacramento and Reno I feel
like a nice Starbucks at a nice wooded
area that I went to one time when I was
listening to battle raps drinking so
much a lot
both driving kind of
all of adventures yeah
Benny
I think maybe we leave the periscope for
now yeah we'll be back
we've got a lot of time together a lot
of ways to go but you follow us twitter
or come okay I for all the ladies two
periscopes we will have some awesome
announcements we've been asking about
today what we're showing you is the
volunteer work for you I am saying that
we will be releasing this again and
we'll see some of you guys soon we'll
see something Sofia